Guide to the Records of the Women's Philharmonic M1470
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series XV: Production Materials
  - Heroes for the Planet Concert
    This file contains correspondence, contracts, repertoire discussions and related planning materials for this April 15 2000 concert. Conductor Marin Alsop was hired to conduct the Women's Philharmonic for this event which was sponsored by the Ford compnay and was held at San Francisco's Masonic Auditorium.
    - April 15, 2000 Concert: "Heroes for the Planet" (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - April 15, 2000 Fee Concert notes (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Concert production correspondence and materials for April 15, 2000 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - 1999-2000 Season notes (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - 1998-1999 Season (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - 2000-2001 Season (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - March 25, 2000 Concert production materials (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - March 10, 2001 Concert (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - May 2000 concert production and program materials (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Chen Yi 2001 concert (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - May 26, 2000 production and venue materials (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Herbst Theater and Green Room notes 2000-2001 season (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - May 26, 2000 Concert: Herbst Theater contract and Green room (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Sept. 26, 2000 production (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - Nov. 24, 2001 Production (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - March 10, 2001 production (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - May 13, 2001 production (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - "Sing It. Tell It" production (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - May 12, 2001 concert reception (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - Peet's Coffee donation correspondence (Box 126, Folder 17)
  - Water donation: Trinity Springs (Box 126, Folder 18)
  - Just desserts donation (Box 126, Folder 19)
  - Flowers donation: Ms. Daisy (Box 126, Folder 20)
  - Pre-paid parking/maps/driving instructions (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - 2000-2001 Season: ticket comps (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Ticket Sales Survey (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Reception: concert checklist, signs and forms (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Reception: food donations (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Reception: food donation, Asks (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Reception: 1999-2000 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Reception: 1998-1999 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Volunteer materials (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - May 28: Salon, Volunteers (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Volunteers for concerts (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Volunteers - History (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - 10/16/1999: Concert Production/Program (Box 130, Folder 13)
  - 1999-2000: Post Concert salons (Box 130, Folder 14)
  - 2001/2002 Season Planning (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - 2000/2001 Season (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - 2001/2002 Season cancellation (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Misc. Production Materials (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Production Notes: September 29, 2001 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - 2001-2002 Season notes (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Herbst Theater Contract, 2003 (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Festival 2004/2005 (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - Program Notes, 2004 (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - Green Room Rental and American Women Masters Materials (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - Open Minds Festival materials (Box 142, Folder 11)
  - Fanfares Project materials (Box 142, Folder 12)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt concert and Hilary Clinton letter (Box 142, Folder 13)
  - Music requests (Box 142, Folder 14)
  - USCF Spring Fundraiser, May 26, 2000 (Box 142, Folder 15)
  - Season Brochure mailing, 1997 (Box 142, Folder 16)
  - Brochure meeting, 3/17/2000 (Box 142, Folder 17)
  - St. Mary's College, 2/26/2000 (Box 142, Folder 18)
  - Nina Kotova (cellist) concert production materials (Box 142, Folder 19)
  - GALA, 2000-2001 (Box 142, Folder 20)
  - Hotel needs, September 30, 2000 (Box 142, Folder 21)
  - Spirituals Project materials, November 2000 (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Chen Yi concert, March 10, 2000 (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Stanford correspondence re. March 10, 2000 concert (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Program Notes, 1998-1999 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - 1998/1999 Season comp (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - November 14th: program (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Roosevelt Concert, December 10, 1998 (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - A Wine Country Celebration, 03/1998: The WP Woodwind Quintet (Box 151, Folder 9)
  - Women for Wine Sense (Box 151, Folder 10)
  - Mills College, 1996-1997 (Box 151, Folder 11)
  - Special Events (Box 151, Folder 12)
  - Fanfares, the Movie (Box 151, Folder 13)
  - The Chen Yi Collaboration, 1996-1997 (Box 151, Folder 14)
  - Education (Box 151, Folder 15)
  - Chen Yi and Music Education notes (Box 151, Folder 16)
  - Music Camp for Women, 1998 (Box 151, Folder 17)
  - Artistic / Educational ideas, 1993 (Box 151, Folder 18)
  - Education Ideas, 1998 (Box 151, Folder 19)
  - 1996-1997 Season (Box 151, Folder 20)
  - GIGS, 1994 (Box 151, Folder 21)
  - 1989-1990 Season Production Notes (Box 165, Folder 8)
  - Women's Philharmonic: Miscellaneous pins and stickers (Box 172, Folder 7)
- Series XVI: Fanfares Project
  Women's Philharmonic "Fanfares"
  To celebrate the new millenium, the Women's Philharmonic commissioned ten American women composers to write pieces. This was a collaborative effort with the Lubbock Symphony and the American Composers Symphony.
  - Fanfares (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Fanfares (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Fanfares Budget (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Fanfares: call for scores (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Fanfares (composers of color; Apo recommendations, etc.) (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - 2/1/1999 Fanfare Funders (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Fanfare (final) (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Fanfares-general file (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Fanfares (temp. file) 9/99 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Fanfares Project (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - 2001 Commissioning Fanfares, materials + notes (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Fanfares video materials (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Fanfares: final commissions materials (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Fanfares notes + materials (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Fanfares project + NEA funding (1998) materials (Box 101, Folder 13)
- Series XVII:"Women of Note" Newsletter materials
  "Women of Note"
  A newsletter published quarterly by the Women's Philharmonic, this contains items relating to its contents, rough drafts, final versions and design materials.
  - Misc. Newsletter Layout (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Newsletter (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Newsletter Misc. (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters 92/93 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Newsletter #2 11/92 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Newsletter #3 1993 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - 11/95 Newsletter--Final (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Women of Note (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Women of Note WP Newsletters 1992-2001 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Newsletter Summer 1996 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Women of Note Spring 1998 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Women of Note Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Women of Note Winter 2000 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Women of Note Spring 2003 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Women of Note Photos for Printing (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Newsletter (Fall) (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Newsletter Spring 2003 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Fall 2003 Newsletter (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Newsletter/Design Vendors (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - 1999 Newsletter and Brochures (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - 1999 Newsletter in progress (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Fall 1998-1999 Fall Newsletter and Misc. Materials (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - WP Newsletter 1999/2000 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Women of Note newsletter, Spring 1999 (Box 146, Folder 13)
  - Women of Note newsletter, 2000-2001 (Box 146, Folder 14)
  - Women of Note newsletter, Summer 2000 (Box 146, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous copies (Box 146, Folder 16)
  - February Newsletter (Box 146, Folder 17)
  - Series XXII: Women's Philharmonic Chamber Ensembles (Box 67, Folder 11)
    Women's Philharmonic Chamber Ensembles
    This file contains repertoire lists; production and correspondence notes; player rosters and advertising relating to the small chamber ensembles that were created using musicians from the larger Women's Philharmonic Orchestra.
    - Chamber ensemble bookings (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Fairbanks Alaska Woodwind Quintet res. Nov. 8-12, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Chamber Ensembles materials/notes (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Chamber Music series 1995-1996 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Women's Phil. chamber ensembles 1997-1998 materials (Box 117, Folder 20)
- Series XVIII: Women's Phil. Musician Roster/Materials
  Orchestra Musicians
  This contains a listing of the various full-time, part-time and substitute members of the Women's Philharmonic. Also included are memos, correspondences and announcements regarding auditions, pay scale and music part assignments.
  - Application for Audition (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Active Players (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Auditions 1989 Cello (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - 1994-95 Chamber Ensemble (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Instrumentation Sheets Rehearsal (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Orchestra soloist Fee Tracking (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Orchestra Players Roster (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - March 3, 1990 Concert Personnel (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Musician Lists/Agreements 1989 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Player Letters 1989-90 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Policies & Provisions (Musician Pay) (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Repertoire and Personnel Lists 9/1989 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Women's Philharmonic Low Brass section (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Women's Philharmonic Brass Section (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Payment Plan for Players (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Player Roster (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Player Committee (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Women's Philharmonic Personnel 5/1992 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Bay Area Women's Philharmonic-1988-89 Audition Repertoire Lists (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Percussion (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - 1999 Recording Agreement with Orchestra (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - 1999 Letter of Agreement: Taping of Eleanor Roosevelt Concert (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - 1992 Orchestra personnel (Box 89, Folder 10)
- Series XIX: National Womens Composers Resource Center (NWCRC)
  National Women's Composers Recource Center
  An initiative of the Women's Philharmonic, the National Women's Composers Resource Center (NWCRC) was founded to encourage composition of new works by female composers. This file includes internal correspondence regarding the establishing and funding of the NWCRC; letters of inquiry from composers; calls for new scores; catalogs listing women composers, their biographical materials and publishing information.
  - National Womens Composers Resource Center (NWCRC) (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - National Womens Composers Resource Center (NWRC) (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - National Womens Composers Resource Center (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Nat'l Womens Resource Center Info (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Nat'l Womens Resource Center Queries; 2000 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 1992 Composer Inquiries and Proposals: NWCRC Commissions (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - NWCRC 1992 materials (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - NWCRC Contract Tape (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - 1994-95 NWCRC Requests (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - NWCRC Misc 1993 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - NWCRC materials 1991-1993 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - NWCRC Requests 1994 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - NWCRC to be logged 1992 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - NWCRC Staff 1992-1994 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - NWCRC 1991-1993 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - NWCRC: How to Catalog Scores (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - NWCRC Requests (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Financials 1991-93 NWCRC (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - NWC Resource Center Timeline (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Nat'l Womens Composers Resource Center/ Compilation stats (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Nat'l Womens Composers Resource Center Invoices 1993 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Nat'l Womens Composers Resource Center Committee (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Nat'l Women's Philharmonic Resource Center: Queries 96-97 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - NWCRC Request Update Reports (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - NWCRC Commpleted Requests (Ensembles) 1991-92 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - NWCRC Completed Requests--Ensembles 1991-92 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - NWCRC Completed Requests --Individuals 1991-92 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - NWC Resource Center form letters (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - 3/31/1996 Women's Phil. Resource center planning (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - 1993 NWCRC Assesment (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - 1990 NWCRC misc. correspondence (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - NWCRC Promotion materials (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - Nat'l Women Composers Resource Center: processing scores (how to) (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Misc. Correspondence: female composers + compositions (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - !993-1994 Nat'l Womens Composers Res. Center materials (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - 1993 Nat'l Womens Composers Res. Center: report (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - 1993 Nat'l womens Composers Res. Center: correspondence (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - 1993 Nat'l Womens Composers Res. Center: correspondence (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - 1992 NWCRC Materials (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - NWCRC + Association of California Symphony Orchestras (ACSO) Materials 1992 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - 1992 NWCRC Materials (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Resource Center general information (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Resource Center materials 1996 - 1998 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Call for Scores posting 2000 - 2001 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Requests 1993-94 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Nat'l Women Composers Resource Center forms, lists and letters (Box 123, Folder 1)
- Series XX: Professional Organization Memberships/Resources
  Professional Organization Memberships
  This includes the various professional organizations in which the Women's Philharmonic had either a membership in or had alliances with: the Bay Area Career Women; American Symphony Orchestra League and the Association of California Symphony Orchestras to name a few.
  - Alliance of California Symphony Orchestras 1991-1992 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Alliance of California Symphony Orchestras (ACSO) continued, 1995 (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Alliance of California Symphony Orchestras (ACSO) 1990-1993 (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - Alliance of California Symphony Orchestras (ACSO) 1997 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Alliance of California Symphony Orchestras (ACSO) 1996 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Alliance of California Symphony Orchestras (ACSO), 1999 (Box 146, Folder 12)
  - Alliance of California Symphony Orchestras + Calif. Composers Showcase materials 1991 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - American Composers Alliance (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - American Composers Forum 1996 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - American Composers Forum 1997 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - American Composers Orchestra Inc. 1996 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - American Music Center 1997 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - American Federation of Musician's (AFM) collective bargaining agreement (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - American Society of Composers,Authors, Publishers (ASCAP) Award Application 2001 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League Concert 6/24/1989 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League: statistics 1991 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League 1993 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League 1993 (trip folder) (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - American Symphony Orchetsra League (ASOL) 1993 and earlier (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League (ASOL) 1995-1996 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League (ASOL) 1996 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League (ASOL) 1997 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League (ASOL): Fellows 1999-2000 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League (ASOL) 2002/03 Program Report (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League (ASOL) 2002/03 Program Report (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League (ASOL): National Conductor Preview Nominations 1999 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Arts Democratic Club Spring 1996 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Arts Management Institute 1998 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - ASCAP award, 1998-1999 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - ASCAP award application, 1997/1998 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - ASCAP 1999-2000 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - ASCAP awards (ASOL) (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - ASCAP (Part I) (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - ASCAP (Part II) (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - ASCAP (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - ASCAP / BMI (Box 144, Folder 10)
  - Bay Area Business Women (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Bay Area Business Women (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Bay Area Career Women (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Bay Area Career Women (BACW): Newsletters 1997-1998 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Bay Area Performing Arts Facilities Conference 1997 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Broadcast Music, Inc. (BMI) 1999 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Business Womens Organizations (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Eugene Symphony (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - International Alliance of Women Musicians (IAWM) (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - International Alliance for Women in Music (IAWM) (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - International Association of Women Musicians (IAWM) (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - International Association of Women Musicians (IAWM) Membership (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Internatioanl Womens Brass Conference (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - International Museum of Women (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Institute for the Musical Arts (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Leadership Programs California (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Membership Renewal: 2000 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Misc. Artist Management inquiries (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Misc. Organizations (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - NAWBO (National Association of Women Business Owners) (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Nat'l Assoc. of Performing Arts Managers and Agents (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - NCLR (National Center on Lesbian Rights) (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - New York Women Composers (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Organizations for Women Composers (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - 21st Century Music (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Red Sky Films (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Resourceful Women Organization (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - San Francisco Women's Centers (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Symphonic Orchestra Institute (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Women in Real Estate (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Women in Technology (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - The Women's Memorial: Women in the Military (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - WAAA (Western Alliance Arts Administrators) (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - San Francisco Planning and Urban Research Assoc. (SPUR) (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Villa Montalvo venue (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Womens Building 1995 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Women's Forum West (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - 1997 Misc. Orchestra News (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Ars Femina ensemble 1992 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - SF Chamber of Commerce (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - American Federation of Musicians (AFM) Master Agreement october 1998-Sept. 2000 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Bus. & Prof. Women (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League Mailing List (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - California Music Society (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - ASOL A.C.S.O. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - June: American Symphony Orchestra League 1989 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Misc. Womens Arts/Business Info (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - BMI (Box 144, Folder 14)
  - International Women's Brass Conference, 1997 report (Box 144, Folder 15)
  - Business Arts Council (Box 144, Folder 16)
  - Business Volunteers for the Arts (Box 144, Folder 17)
  - California Institute for the Arts (Box 144, Folder 18)
  - California Lawyers for the Arts (Box 144, Folder 19)
  - California NOW conference (Box 144, Folder 20)
  - Chinatown Community Development Center (Box 144, Folder 21)
  - The College Music Society (Box 144, Folder 22)
  - Project Plans and Job Description (Box 144, Folder 23)
  - Job Description: Artistic Program Coordinator (Box 144, Folder 24)
  - City Box Office, 2004 (Box 144, Folder 25)
  - Gay Men's Chorus, correspondence (Box 144, Folder 26)
  - Beijing + 5, correspondence (Feb. 26, 2000) (Box 144, Folder 27)
  - Budget, 2000 (Box 144, Folder 28)
  - Women in Business Project (Box 144, Folder 29)
  - Misc. correspondence, 1992-1998 (Box 144, Folder 30)
  - Rebeka Brady flight itinerary (Box 144, Folder 31)
- Series XXI: Recording Sessions
  Recording Sessions
  This includes production materials, various correspondence related to logistics, budget and repertoire.
  - Leslie Ann Jones (audio engineer) (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - 5/9/1992 Recording Concert (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Recordings (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Walker Recording 2003 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Recording session 6/1996 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Classic CD Award; 2nd Koch Recording (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 5/30/1999 Price Recording Sessions (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Price Recording 1999-2000 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - 1999-2000 March recording sessions (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Sound Recording Payments (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Fundraising materials for recoding (March 1992) (Box 107, Folder 25)
  - Phonograph Record Manufacturers' Special Payments Fund (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Recording materials/notes (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Sony Transfer (Box 52, Folder 19)
- Series XXIII: Inaugural Years materials
  Inaugural season
  This includes correspondences of Elizabeth Seja Min, Nan Washburn and Miriam Abrams, the founders of the Women's Philharmonic. The majority of the material is from the early 1980s and represents the organization's first ten years. This series includes audtion calls for various orchestral instruments; letters of inquiry from conductors, musicians and guest artists; musician union negotiations and correspondence from musicans; office memos and other correspondences relating to the organizing and development of an orchestra, its repertoire and its concerts. Additional information relating to the Community Women's Orchestra, an amateur orchestra organized by the Women's Philharmonic and conducted by Nan Washburn is also included. These include: program notes; audition announcements; orchestra member surveys and correspondence.
  - Inaugural season planning and correspondence (1981) (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Misc. Office correspondence to Miriam Abrams (1992) (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Elizabeth Min correspondence (1981-1982) (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - Orchestra and staff correspondence (1981-1984) (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - Concerto concert May 17, 1984 materials (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence-misc. musicians (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - Guest artist inquiries and correspondence (1983) (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence-conductors (Box 158, Folder 8)
  - ASCAP application (Box 158, Folder 9)
  - American women composers resources (Box 158, Folder 10)
  - 1987 audition materials (Box 158, Folder 11)
  - Audition correspondence (Box 158, Folder 12)
  - Audition results Sept. 1984 (Box 158, Folder 13)
  - Music excerpts and sightreading materials (Box 158, Folder 14)
  - Audition excerpts and sightreading materials (Box 158, Folder 15)
  - California Arts Council: information and materials (Box 158, Folder 16)
  - Community Women's Orchestra materials (Box 158, Folder 17)
  - Community Women's Orchestra programs and correspondence (Box 158, Folder 18)
  - Inner Office memos, 1985 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Orchestra Personnel and correspondence, 1987 (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Personnel (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Job description material, 1988 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Reorginization 1985: Music Director Search (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - Staff letters and memos: library, personnel, etc. (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - Women's ensembles/orchestras/Panopticon (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - Denver Chamber Orchestra and music rental, 1988 (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - Production, 1988/1989 (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - Leonarda Productions - Marple Hall (Box 159, Folder 10)
  - International League of Women Composers (Box 159, Folder 11)
  - New York Women Composers (Box 159, Folder 12)
  - Staff Memos; job descriptions; player letters (Box 159, Folder 13)
  - International Congress on Women in Music and miscellaneous materials (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Conference and materials, 1985 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1981-1989 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Conference and festivals materials, 1982-1985 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - Resource Center requests (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, general: 1985-1989 (Box 160, Folder 6)
- Series XXIV: Restricted Files
  Restricted files